const BANK = [
  
  // Question 1
  {question: 'What type of car is Elon Musk planning to send to Mars?',
   answers: [
    'A red Geo Metro',
   'A red Saturn Ion',
   'A red Tesla Roadster',
   'A red Tesla Model S'],
   correctAnswer: 'A red Tesla Roadster'},
   
  // Question 2
   {question: 'What is the actual name of SpaceX?',
   answers: [
     'Space Extreme Technologies Corporation',
     'Space Exploration Technologies Corporation',
     'Space Extraterrestrial Technologies Corporation',
     'Space Xtreme Technologies Corporation'],
   correctAnswer: 'Space Exploration Technologies Corporation'},

  // Question 3
   {question: 'What is the Falcon 9 named after?',
   answers: [
     'The Millennium Falcon',
   "Elon Musk's pet falcon",
   'Captain Falco',
   'The Falcon from The Falcon film series in the 1940s'],
   correctAnswer: 'The Millennium Falcon'},

  // Question 4
   {question: 'When did SpaceX become the first private space company to dock with the International Space Station?',
   answers: [
     "They haven't docked with the International Space Station. ",
     '2010',
     '1812, Elon can travel back in time',
     '2012'],
   correctAnswer: '2012'},

  // Question 5
   {question: "Who developed the science experiments for SpaceX's first connection with the ISS?",
   answers: [
     'Albert Einstein',
     '15 Students',
     'Elon Musk',
     'Stephen Hawking'],
   correctAnswer: '15 Students'},

  // Question 6
   {question: 'SpaceX was the first to use Launch Complex 39A at Kennedy Space Center after it was retired. Why is this launch complex famous?',
   answers: [
     "It's where the Apollo 11 moon mission began.",
     "It's where Agent J saved the world.",
     "We found aliens there, but the government covered it up.",
     "It isn't famous."],
   correctAnswer: "It's where the Apollo 11 moon mission began."},

  // Question 7
   {question: 'SpaceX was the first to fly a reusable ____.',
   answers: [
     'orbital class rocket',
     'ion thruster rocket',
     'space shuttle',
     'Starship Enterprise'],
   correctAnswer: 'orbital class rocket'},

  // Question 8
   {question: 'SpaceX is partnering with NASA to make ____.',
   answers: [
     'the best food in the known galaxy',
     'a flying car',
     'space suits',
     'Elon into a cyborg'],
   correctAnswer: 'space suits'},

  // Question 9
   {question: 'How much can the Falcon Heavy rocket carry?',
   answers: [
     '50,000 pounds',
     '75,547 pounds',
     '112,479.5 pounds',
     '119,000 pounds'],
   correctAnswer: '119,000 pounds'},

  // Question 10
   {question: 'What is the Dragon spacecraft named after?',
   answers: [
     'Puff the Magic Dragon',
     'Viserion the Dragon from Game of Thrones',
     'Magellan the Dragon',
     'Smaug the Dragon'],
   correctAnswer: 'Puff the Magic Dragon'}
];